Okay, so now let's talk about
an exciting development which is called AWS Outposts.
What is hybrid cloud?
Businesses that keep an on-premise infrastructure
alongside a cloud infrastructure
are called hybrid cloud.
And when we have that,
we have two ways of dealing with IT systems.
We have one for the cloud of AWS, for example
using the console of AWS, the CLI
and the APIs from AWS,
but also we have another one
that is dedicated to on-premises infrastructure.
And so, that means two different types of skillsets,
two different types of API,
and that may be complicated.
So it was said, "Okay, we do recognize
that some companies will run a hybrid cloud
therefore, let's create Outpost."
And Outpost our server racks
that offer the same AWS infrastructure,
services, API and tools
to build your own application on-premises
just like in the cloud.
So what this means is that
they will come and set up
and manage Outpost racks which are servers
within your on premises infrastructure.
And then these servers come preloaded
with the (indistinct) services
but you can benefit them from on-premises.
So as we can see now on your corporate data center
you will have your Outpost racks directly set up by AWS.
And this allows you to extend
the (indistinct) services directly
onto your on-premises data centers
which is I think revolutionary.
But a difference between an EC2 instance
running on the cloud
and an EC2 instance running in your own data center
is that now you are responsible for their security,
the physical security of the rack itself
because that rack is within your own data center.
The benefits from using Outposts are many,
first of all, you get low latency access
to on-premise the system,
you get local data processing
so the data may actually never leave your on-premise system
and never go to the cloud,
data residency, so again, it lives
within your own data centers.
It's easy for example, to start the migration
from on-premise is to Outpost
and then when you're ready from Outpost to the cloud.
It's a fully managed service.
So AWS will manage the service for you.
And with Outpost for now,
you can launch a lot of services
such as Amazon EC2, Amazon EBS, Amazon S3
Amazon EKS, Amazon ECS, Amazon RDS, and Amazon EMR.
So it's really a cool way to extend the cloud directly
onto your own our infrastructure on-premises system,
and this is revolutionary.
So this may come up in the exam.
I hope you liked it.
And I will see you in the next lecture.